https://www.mww.com/privacy-policy

PRIVACY POLICY - MWWPR | Digital & Content Marketing, Communications and Public Affairs
LOCATIONS
Prospective Client?
Please email Patrick Brady at pbrady@mww.com
Prospective Employee?
Please visit our Careers page
Just have a question?
Please email Amanda Rosa at arosa@mww.com
MWW Group is committed to protecting your privacy and maintaining your confidence and trust. As such, we openly communicate our privacy practices to visitors to our website. We have created the following privacy policy to openly communicate how we collect and use information.
MWW Group does not collect any information without your knowledge and permission. We collect general, non-personally identifiable information that we use to improve our site, such as your browser type, geographic area, or the server your computer is logged onto. We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent. There may be pages on our website upon which we ask for personal information such as your name and e-mail address. The information we collect is used for internal purposes only (to properly handle requests for additional information, etc.). Information that you supply to MWW Group is stored in a secure location and is accessible only by designated staff. We do not share your personal information with any other organizations or third parties for commercial purposes.
The data collected from visitors to our site is analyzed in aggregate form to show trends and improve the website for future visits. We do not record personally identifiable information. Like most public websites, our site collects your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the number that is assigned to your computer when you connect to the Internet, when you log on to our site. This information is used to gather information about our visitors’ browsing actions for composite use only.
IF YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT THE SECURITY AT OUR WEBSITE, PLEASE E-MAIL US AT HELPDESK@MWW.COM.
Prospective Client?
Please email Patrick Brady at pbrady@mww.com
Prospective Employee?
Please visit our Careers page
Just have a question?
Please email Amanda Rosa at arosa@mww.com
© 2020 MWW GROUP
[/one_half
Your browser does not support the video tag.
My name here
It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when lookin
